

ΚΕΝΤΡΟ ΕΠΙΜΟΡΦΩΣΗΣ ΚΑΙ ΔΙΑ ΒΙΟΥ ΜΑΘΗΣΗΣ

# **Aσκήσεις / Challenges**

Αθ. Ανδρούτσος



## Άσκηση 1

### Προγραμματισμός με Java



### • Υλοποιήστε το παραπάνω mockup

2



## Άσκηση 2

### Προγραμματισμός με Java

← → C ① 127	7.0.0.1:5500/ch1/form.html		
Αίτηση Συμμε	ετοχής		
Προσωπικά Στοιχε	εία		
Όνομα:	Επώνυμο:	Πατρώνυμο:	
Στοιχεία Κατοικία	Ş		
Διεύθυνση Κατοικίας:	Αριθμός:	TK:	
Στοιχεία Επικοινωνίας			
Τηλέφωνο:	Αριθμός:		

• Υλοποιήστε το παραπάνω mockup



## Άσκηση 3

Προγραμματισμός με Java

### **Andreas Andreadis**

#### Personal information

Email: andreas@gmail.com

Phone number: 0310554540

Address: 4, Rue de Verdun, 71300 MONTCEAU-LES-

MINES



#### **Profile**

Experienced developer with more than 5 years of experience in full-stack programming. Expert in data analysis and problem solving, with great attention to detail and a strong ability to work under pressure. He also has significant experience in personnel management and project supervision.

#### Professional experience :

October 2019 - present Mid Developer

XYZ Company, Athens, Greece

- Java
- C#
- Angular

Jan 2017 – Sept 2019 Junior Developer

ABC Company, Athens, Greece

- · Assist the developer team
- Verification and validation of tests
- · Creation and updating of customer info

Jan 2016 - Sept 2016 Internship

ABC Company, Athens, Greece

- · Preparation of mockups
- Assistance in monthly testing

ting

Education:		
September 2016 - June 2017	ber 2016 - June MSc in Computing, University of Athens, Greece	
Jan 2012 – Sept 2016	BSc in Computing, University of Patras, Greece	

 Δημιουργήστε το CV χωρίς το styling (borders και colors)

4